MARK VINCENT ESTRADA

CONTACT



+639457194445 / +639474261330



estrada.markvincent.ccs@gmail.com



Kapasigan, Pasig City



OBJECTIVE

Taking Bachelor of Science in Computer Science at Pamantasan ng Lungsod ng Pasig (PLP), I aim to gather knowledge and experience to refine my current skills and acquire additional set of skills. This will not only benefit me and my university but your company as well by being a good role model

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

2019 - July 2023

Pamantasan ng Lungsod ng

Pasiq

Achievements

Second Year - Fourth Year Dean's Lister

Third Year - President Lister

WORK EXPERIENCE

SPES, Pasig City Hall

Pasig City Mar 2015 - April 2015

- Assisting medical personnels in carrying medical equipment during visits on different barangays.
- Helping in encoding patient's information using microsoft excel

Intern at Wellness PRO Inc.

Kapitolyo, Pasig City March 2023 - April 2023

- Digitalizing employee 201 files and Service Reports
- RFID Encoding
- Designing company website using WordPress

SKILLS

- MIT App Inventor / Kodular
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- WordPress
- C++
- Time Management
- Work Ethic